<?xml version="1.0"?>
<pnp:Provisioning xmlns:pnp="http://schemas.dev.office.com/PnP/2021/03/ProvisioningSchema">
  <pnp:Preferences Generator="PnP.Framework, Version=1.5.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=null" />
  <pnp:Templates ID="CONTAINER-TEMPLATE-8244CC8F0E234221B583EFE09419975E">
    <pnp:ProvisioningTemplate ID="TEMPLATE-8244CC8F0E234221B583EFE09419975E" Version="1" BaseSiteTemplate="SITEPAGEPUBLISHING#0" Scope="RootSite">
      <pnp:ClientSidePages>
        <pnp:ClientSidePage PromoteAsNewsArticle="true" PromoteAsTemplate="false" Overwrite="true" Title="Traverse your digital workplace" ThumbnailUrl="" PageName="Traverse-your-digital-workplace.aspx">
          <pnp:Header Type="Custom" ServerRelativeImageUrl="https://cdn.hubblecontent.osi.office.net/m365content/publish/40a79bdc-d5a1-4e60-abc8-8c1a705c3743/gettyimages-1221754481.jpg" LayoutType="CutInShape" ShowTopicHeader="false" ShowPublishDate="false" TopicHeader="" AlternativeText="" Authors="[{&quot;id&quot;:&quot;i:0#.f|membership|USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;upn&quot;:&quot;USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;email&quot;:&quot;USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;John Smith&quot;,&quot;role&quot;:&quot;&quot;}]" AuthorByLine="[&quot;i:0#.f|membership|USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;]" AuthorByLineId="7" />
          <pnp:Sections>
            <pnp:Section Order="1" Type="OneColumn">
              <pnp:Controls>
                <pnp:CanvasControl WebPartType="Text" ControlId="1212fc8d-dd6b-408a-8d5d-9f1cc787efbb" Order="1" Column="1">
                  <pnp:CanvasControlProperties>
                    <pnp:CanvasControlProperty Key="Text" Value="&lt;p&gt;LiveTiles Everywhere is like a teleportation device for your digital workplace. This ever-present panel lets you effortlessly slide between core business tools while working on the go in MS Teams and SharePoint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Materialise the essentials&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Summon the tools you need to complete your mission. Light up and launch the most relevant corporate content and business functionality. Reveal and conceal business apps, personal links, service menus, and more, in a few clicks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Platforms unite!&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everywhere seamlessly integrates with your SharePoint and Teams environments.&amp;nbsp; Universally available from the left-hand side in SharePoint and the header in Teams, Everywhere unites your intranet with this power-couple of platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Right on target&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deliver personalized and customized content to whomever you choose. Populate your panel with content and functionality relevant to everyone across your organisation then curate information targeted to specific audiences and groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The search is over&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Save time searching intranet pages to find what you need. Quickly access your core functionality, content, and business tools unified in both SharePoint and Teams.&amp;nbsp; Wherever you’re working, Everywhere is there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Launch at warp speed&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a complete cloud application the installation and onboarding process is lighting fast and code-free.&amp;nbsp; Automatically connect and deploy the LiveTiles Everywhere application to your SharePoint environment within minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;" />
                  </pnp:CanvasControlProperties>
                </pnp:CanvasControl>
                <pnp:CanvasControl WebPartType="Custom" JsonControlData="{&quot;id&quot;: &quot;544dd15b-cf3c-441b-96da-004d5a8cea1d&quot;, &quot;instanceId&quot;: &quot;c5029ff2-f2f2-41e2-b3aa-73cd34e2fd5a&quot;, &quot;title&quot;: &quot;YouTube&quot;, &quot;description&quot;: &quot;Show a YouTube video on the page.&quot;, &quot;dataVersion&quot;: &quot;1.2&quot;, &quot;properties&quot;: {&quot;embedCode&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/QRxOpqJs4ms&quot;,&quot;shouldScaleWidth&quot;:true,&quot;thumbnailUrl&quot;:&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QRxOpqJs4ms/hqdefault.jpg&quot;,&quot;webPartContentUrl&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;runtimeState&quot;:{&quot;isPrivate&quot;:false,&quot;showControls&quot;:true},&quot;cachedEmbedCode&quot;:&quot;&lt;iframe width=\&quot;200\&quot; height=\&quot;113\&quot; src=\&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/QRxOpqJs4ms?feature=oembed\&quot; frameborder=\&quot;0\&quot; allowfullscreen=\&quot;\&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&quot;,&quot;cachedEmbedCodeThumbnail&quot;:&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QRxOpqJs4ms/hqdefault.jpg&quot;}, &quot;serverProcessedContent&quot;: {&quot;htmlStrings&quot;:{},&quot;searchablePlainTexts&quot;:{},&quot;imageSources&quot;:{},&quot;links&quot;:{}}, &quot;dynamicDataPaths&quot;: {}, &quot;dynamicDataValues&quot;: {}}" ControlId="544dd15b-cf3c-441b-96da-004d5a8cea1d" Order="2" Column="1" />
              </pnp:Controls>
            </pnp:Section>
          </pnp:Sections>
        </pnp:ClientSidePage>
        <pnp:ClientSidePage PromoteAsNewsArticle="true" PromoteAsTemplate="false" Overwrite="true" Title="Mobilise your teams" ThumbnailUrl="" PageName="Mobilise.aspx">
          <pnp:Header Type="Custom" ServerRelativeImageUrl="https://cdn.hubblecontent.osi.office.net/m365content/publish/93962e27-cc71-4fd9-a806-1f95329ca3bd/gettyimages-707456495_super.jpg" LayoutType="CutInShape" ShowTopicHeader="false" ShowPublishDate="false" TopicHeader="" AlternativeText="" Authors="[{&quot;id&quot;:&quot;i:0#.f|membership|USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;upn&quot;:&quot;USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;email&quot;:&quot;USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;John Smith&quot;,&quot;role&quot;:&quot;&quot;}]" AuthorByLine="[&quot;i:0#.f|membership|USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;]" AuthorByLineId="7" />
          <pnp:Sections>
            <pnp:Section Order="1" Type="OneColumn">
              <pnp:Controls>
                <pnp:CanvasControl WebPartType="Text" ControlId="1212fc8d-dd6b-408a-8d5d-9f1cc787efbb" Order="1" Column="1">
                  <pnp:CanvasControlProperties>
                    <pnp:CanvasControlProperty Key="Text" Value="&lt;h4&gt;Free your comms from the desktop&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;From HQ to the outer reaches of your workplace, the&amp;nbsp;Reach&amp;nbsp;mobile app keeps all workers in the loop, regardless of location and device. Installed from the app store, Reach lets you securely interact with news, posts, pages, people, and events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Converse across the cosmos&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEWS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reach makes communicating easy,&amp;nbsp;independent of location, time,&amp;nbsp;and device. Target information to external staff such as freelancers and contractors, saving time transferring internal info.&amp;nbsp; Overcome language barriers with Reach’s automatic translation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Stay in the loop&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;POSTS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chat and connect with your team, anywhere, anytime. With LiveTiles Reach it doesn’t matter if you’re at a desk, on a loading bay, or helping clients. Post a news item in a few clicks, check new social posts, engage with co-workers, and stay on top of business updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Share at light speed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAGES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make knowledge available to your non-desk workers right where they need it.&amp;nbsp; Provide important information, policies, forms and employee handbooks in a structured way. Keep content always current and provide the latest updates through push notifications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Know who's who in the crew&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;PEOPLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quickly find contact information for all your co-workers to communicate by phone, chat, or mail.&amp;nbsp; Search for skills in our enhanced profiles to find experts.&amp;nbsp; Include external contacts to quickly find peers outside your organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Join the cyber-party&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVENTS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organize and promote staff events, fun activities, town hall meetings, and training.&amp;nbsp; Manage registrations and special attendee requirements and gather feedback through integrated polls.&amp;nbsp; Make sure agenda updates or important changes are seen by the right people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;" />
                  </pnp:CanvasControlProperties>
                </pnp:CanvasControl>
                <pnp:CanvasControl WebPartType="Custom" JsonControlData="{&quot;id&quot;: &quot;544dd15b-cf3c-441b-96da-004d5a8cea1d&quot;, &quot;instanceId&quot;: &quot;c5029ff2-f2f2-41e2-b3aa-73cd34e2fd5a&quot;, &quot;title&quot;: &quot;YouTube&quot;, &quot;description&quot;: &quot;Show a YouTube video on the page.&quot;, &quot;dataVersion&quot;: &quot;1.2&quot;, &quot;properties&quot;: {&quot;embedCode&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/WYvMtJl15Es&quot;,&quot;shouldScaleWidth&quot;:true,&quot;thumbnailUrl&quot;:&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WYvMtJl15Es/maxresdefault.jpg&quot;,&quot;webPartContentUrl&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;runtimeState&quot;:{&quot;isPrivate&quot;:false,&quot;showControls&quot;:true},&quot;cachedEmbedCode&quot;:&quot;&lt;iframe width=\&quot;200\&quot; height=\&quot;113\&quot; src=\&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/WYvMtJl15Es?feature=oembed\&quot; frameborder=\&quot;0\&quot; allowfullscreen=\&quot;\&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&quot;,&quot;cachedEmbedCodeThumbnail&quot;:&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WYvMtJl15Es/maxresdefault.jpg&quot;}, &quot;serverProcessedContent&quot;: {&quot;htmlStrings&quot;:{},&quot;searchablePlainTexts&quot;:{},&quot;imageSources&quot;:{},&quot;links&quot;:{}}, &quot;dynamicDataPaths&quot;: {}, &quot;dynamicDataValues&quot;: {}}" ControlId="544dd15b-cf3c-441b-96da-004d5a8cea1d" Order="2" Column="1" />
              </pnp:Controls>
            </pnp:Section>
          </pnp:Sections>
        </pnp:ClientSidePage>
        <pnp:ClientSidePage PromoteAsNewsArticle="true" PromoteAsTemplate="false" Overwrite="true" Title="The digital workplace perfected" ThumbnailUrl="" PageName="The-digital-workplace-perfected.aspx">
          <pnp:Header Type="Custom" ServerRelativeImageUrl="https://cdn.hubblecontent.osi.office.net/m365content/publish/bbffc46e-a046-4812-b6ae-b00e2639603e/gettyimages-879809148.jpg" LayoutType="CutInShape" ShowTopicHeader="false" ShowPublishDate="false" TopicHeader="" AlternativeText="" Authors="[{&quot;id&quot;:&quot;i:0#.f|membership|USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;upn&quot;:&quot;USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;email&quot;:&quot;USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;John Smith&quot;,&quot;role&quot;:&quot;&quot;}]" AuthorByLine="[&quot;i:0#.f|membership|USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;]" AuthorByLineId="7" />
          <pnp:Sections>
            <pnp:Section Order="1" Type="OneColumn">
              <pnp:Controls>
                <pnp:CanvasControl WebPartType="Text" ControlId="1212fc8d-dd6b-408a-8d5d-9f1cc787efbb" Order="1" Column="1">
                  <pnp:CanvasControlProperties>
                    <pnp:CanvasControlProperty Key="Text" Value="&lt;p&gt;We’ve taken the best of our workplace tech and crafted it into two phenomenal intranet solutions. Enterprise: A broad and deep end-to-end solution used by some of the world’s largest organisations, and Hub: A simple single-pane-of-glass solution that brings together news, content, and information, simply and powerfully. Both revolutionary. Both game-changing. Select the style that works best for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Captain the enterprise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take charge of your workplace journey with our award-winning enterprise intranet.&amp;nbsp; Enterprise is jam-packed with every capability you need to create a solution that meets all your organization’s requirements…and then some.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Discover an extensive set of highly configurable features geared to boost digital productivity and deliver highly sophisticated enterprise communication and collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Power up with News Engine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;From Twitter, Instagram, and RSS feeds to peer-to-peer messages and global and local company news, the news engine is where all news and information is created and distributed in a personalized news aggregation point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news hub can be surfaced on any SharePoint page or from the LiveTiles Everywhere panel where news can be delivered in whatever app people are working in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use&amp;nbsp;the intuitive news editor for peer-to-peer communication and use the integration features to create a&amp;nbsp;handy&amp;nbsp;newsfeed&amp;nbsp;from all relevant sources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Mega menu&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mega menu feature offers a customizable global navigation for your intranet that can span across multiple hubs and site collections and bind together Classic and Modern SharePoint sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create a menu with rich media content like images, GIFs, and video using the mega menu’s HTML editor with text formatting tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use the built-in language engine to support navigation on a multilingual intranet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create menus customized to different audiences with the mega menu’s target audience management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multi-site configuration. Build a mega menu than spans across content on an entire tenant or build different mega menus for different parts of your intranet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bridge the worlds of modern and classic SharePoint sites. Build a mega menu that spans across classic and modern sites&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Governance and collaborative workspaces&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enable users to intuitively provision workspaces at the same time as you meet the business’ need for governance. The workspaces module enables seamless provisioning and governance of workspaces within SharePoint and Teams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Streamline creation and governance of collaboration spaces and bridge the workspace experience across SharePoint and Teams. From project rooms, extranets, communities of practice, ideation sites, subject matter spaces, department sites, committee rooms – including advanced features for governance and provisioning – the workspace feature is designed to support all types of enterprise collaboration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design workspaces for every business purpose. Workspace templates are designed and governed by the admin and can include unique news channels, metadata, project roles, and permission settings&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Peer-to-peer communication&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;By&amp;nbsp;using LiveTiles&amp;nbsp;News Engine for peer-to-peer messaging, you&amp;nbsp;give both&amp;nbsp;editors and end users an intuitive experience that makes writing, commenting, and reading news available to everyone in your organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Built-in content governance and compliance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensure your people are compliant. Employees are automatically notified of policies. A built-in page control prompts employees to actively confirm they have read required content&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Delegated content contact and owner. Policy pages include fields to define page contact as well as primary and secondary owners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a policy page has been edited, the page will be published in a new version. All versions of a policy page are stored&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compliance reporting. The included compliance report lets intranet admins track whether critical information and new versions of policy pages are read by all employees. The report provides detailed information and enables you to gently nudge employees who need a reminder to catch up on their reading&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Content targeting&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Create a personalized experience and save users time finding information by delivering ultra-targeted content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Reveal your intranet’s hidden beauty&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAGE DESIGNER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deliver pages, portals and dashboards with the consumer-grade design quality employees have come to also expect from enterprise software. Use the 70+ preconfigured tiles across a drag-and-drop WYSIWYG canvas, the Page Designer tool allows you to completely control the look and feel of your intranet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your ready-to-go intranet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;LiveTiles Intranet Hub is a ready-to-run solution. It makes use of Search and Microsoft Graph, can surface content from across your entire Office 365 instance, and other cloud platforms. It gives you easy access to all your content and tools in an appealing user interface on any device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Enterprise-ready solutions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;GREAT O365 INTEGRATION A state-of-the-art intranet advancing Microsoft’s offering into enterprise-ready solutions, underpinned by governance and compliance, unified communication, information, collaboration and processes across Office 365 and Microsoft Teams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Reveal your intranet’s hidden beauty&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAGE DESIGNER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deliver pages, portals, and dashboards with the consumer-grade design quality employees have come to expect from enterprise software. Use the 70+ preconfigured tiles across a drag-and-drop WYSIWYG canvas. The Page Designer tool allows you to completely control the look and feel of your intranet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The hub of your digital universe&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;LiveTiles Intranet Hub has been conceived and designed from a pure user perspective, adopting the digital workplace concept of reuniting communication, social collaboration and knowledge sharing on one single platform that can be provided in any work context.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LiveTiles Intranet Hub provides a rich feature set in a central portal leveraging the entire Office 365 platform that can be used by your employees on any device to interact with colleagues, collaborate, and share information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Futuristic problem-solving power&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;LiveTiles Hub solves fundamental problems in digital services integration and provides the most complete vision according to Gartner. We develop today what our customers need tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Targeted content Our metadata-based technologies provide a rich search index without management overhead and enable content targeting on semantic relations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speed and agility Workspace templates are designed and governed by the admin, and can include unique news channels, metadata, project roles, and permission settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Our experts have done the work for you&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider 80% of the conceptual work such as UI design, information architecture, and technical specification, done. The best experts in the market have already done this work and embedded the results into LiveTiles Intranet Hub, minimizing your risks in the implementation project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dynamic next gen communications&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Content managers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communicate through defined channels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aggregate content from multiple cloud and on-prem repositories&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Target content based on roles, location, device and topics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Publish content on multiple platforms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Curate content from multiple sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;" />
                  </pnp:CanvasControlProperties>
                </pnp:CanvasControl>
                <pnp:CanvasControl WebPartType="Custom" JsonControlData="{&quot;id&quot;: &quot;544dd15b-cf3c-441b-96da-004d5a8cea1d&quot;, &quot;instanceId&quot;: &quot;c5029ff2-f2f2-41e2-b3aa-73cd34e2fd5a&quot;, &quot;title&quot;: &quot;YouTube&quot;, &quot;description&quot;: &quot;Show a YouTube video on the page.&quot;, &quot;dataVersion&quot;: &quot;1.2&quot;, &quot;properties&quot;: {&quot;embedCode&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/fbMWAqRlO9Y&quot;,&quot;shouldScaleWidth&quot;:true,&quot;thumbnailUrl&quot;:&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fbMWAqRlO9Y/hqdefault.jpg&quot;,&quot;webPartContentUrl&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;runtimeState&quot;:{&quot;isPrivate&quot;:false,&quot;showControls&quot;:true},&quot;cachedEmbedCode&quot;:&quot;&lt;iframe width=\&quot;200\&quot; height=\&quot;113\&quot; src=\&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fbMWAqRlO9Y?feature=oembed\&quot; frameborder=\&quot;0\&quot; allowfullscreen=\&quot;\&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&quot;,&quot;cachedEmbedCodeThumbnail&quot;:&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fbMWAqRlO9Y/hqdefault.jpg&quot;}, &quot;serverProcessedContent&quot;: {&quot;htmlStrings&quot;:{},&quot;searchablePlainTexts&quot;:{},&quot;imageSources&quot;:{},&quot;links&quot;:{}}, &quot;dynamicDataPaths&quot;: {}, &quot;dynamicDataValues&quot;: {}}" ControlId="544dd15b-cf3c-441b-96da-004d5a8cea1d" Order="2" Column="1" />
              </pnp:Controls>
            </pnp:Section>
          </pnp:Sections>
        </pnp:ClientSidePage>
        <pnp:ClientSidePage PromoteAsNewsArticle="true" PromoteAsTemplate="false" Overwrite="true" Title="Take the quantum leap forward" ThumbnailUrl="" PageName="Take-the-quantum-leap-forward.aspx">
          <pnp:Header Type="Custom" ServerRelativeImageUrl="https://cdn.hubblecontent.osi.office.net/m365content/publish/1e9e8a1b-04a2-459c-abb5-fde5f53e3770/gettyimages-1090434684.jpg" LayoutType="CutInShape" ShowTopicHeader="false" ShowPublishDate="false" TopicHeader="" AlternativeText="" Authors="[{&quot;id&quot;:&quot;i:0#.f|membership|USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;upn&quot;:&quot;USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;email&quot;:&quot;USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;,&quot;name&quot;:&quot;John Smith&quot;,&quot;role&quot;:&quot;&quot;}]" AuthorByLine="[&quot;i:0#.f|membership|USER_PLACEHOLDER&quot;]" AuthorByLineId="7" />
          <pnp:Sections>
            <pnp:Section Order="1" Type="OneColumn">
              <pnp:Controls>
                <pnp:CanvasControl WebPartType="Text" ControlId="1212fc8d-dd6b-408a-8d5d-9f1cc787efbb" Order="1" Column="1">
                  <pnp:CanvasControlProperties>
                    <pnp:CanvasControlProperty Key="Text" Value="&lt;h4&gt;Transport your business into the future&lt;br&gt;​​​​​​​&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LiveTiles Quantum&amp;nbsp;is the space-age tool kit you&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;need for powerful business insights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quantum’s modules are driven by artificial intelligence, giving you the power to optimize your digital workplace by connecting data from multiple applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drive your entire workplace experience by data, context, and user behaviour, intelligent employee profiling, and business modelling. Provide automation and support to facilitate daily routines and increase productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get actionable insights into how your solutions are being used and make data-driven decisions to improve user experiences and content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LiveTiles Quantum&amp;nbsp;is the space-age tool kit you need for powerful business insights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quantum’s modules are driven by artificial intelligence, giving you the power to optimize your digital workplace by connecting data from multiple applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drive your entire workplace experience by data, context, and user behaviour, intelligent employee profiling, and business modelling. Provide automation and support to facilitate daily routines and increase productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get actionable insights into how your solutions are being used and make data-driven decisions to improve user experiences and content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;" />
                  </pnp:CanvasControlProperties>
                </pnp:CanvasControl>
                <pnp:CanvasControl WebPartType="Custom" JsonControlData="{&quot;id&quot;: &quot;544dd15b-cf3c-441b-96da-004d5a8cea1d&quot;, &quot;instanceId&quot;: &quot;c5029ff2-f2f2-41e2-b3aa-73cd34e2fd5a&quot;, &quot;title&quot;: &quot;YouTube&quot;, &quot;description&quot;: &quot;Show a YouTube video on the page.&quot;, &quot;dataVersion&quot;: &quot;1.2&quot;, &quot;properties&quot;: {&quot;embedCode&quot;:&quot;https://youtu.be/jEbVEe8628Y&quot;,&quot;shouldScaleWidth&quot;:true,&quot;thumbnailUrl&quot;:&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jEbVEe8628Y/maxresdefault.jpg&quot;,&quot;webPartContentUrl&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;runtimeState&quot;:{&quot;isPrivate&quot;:false,&quot;showControls&quot;:true},&quot;cachedEmbedCode&quot;:&quot;&lt;iframe width=\&quot;200\&quot; height=\&quot;113\&quot; src=\&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jEbVEe8628Y?feature=oembed\&quot; frameborder=\&quot;0\&quot; allowfullscreen=\&quot;\&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&quot;,&quot;cachedEmbedCodeThumbnail&quot;:&quot;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jEbVEe8628Y/maxresdefault.jpg&quot;}, &quot;serverProcessedContent&quot;: {&quot;htmlStrings&quot;:{},&quot;searchablePlainTexts&quot;:{},&quot;imageSources&quot;:{},&quot;links&quot;:{}}, &quot;dynamicDataPaths&quot;: {}, &quot;dynamicDataValues&quot;: {}}" ControlId="544dd15b-cf3c-441b-96da-004d5a8cea1d" Order="2" Column="1" />
              </pnp:Controls>
            </pnp:Section>
          </pnp:Sections>
        </pnp:ClientSidePage>
      </pnp:ClientSidePages>
    </pnp:ProvisioningTemplate>
  </pnp:Templates>
</pnp:Provisioning>

